The morning chime has rung, we are
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
It has begun! Yasumoto King!
Yay!
Yasumoto King!
Aya-chan!
This corner is, right?
We did a project called "Yuna King" before, didn't we?
This is Yasumoto's version.
Who knows the most about Yasumoto among you?
and who knows the most about me?
I'd like you to compete with each other in a quiz format.
I'm sure that today, among all the Ebichu members
I'm sure there is a member who is close to Yasumoto
Really?
Thank you very much
I've gathered people that i'm sure they like Yasumoto...
after all, I've known her since before she was a debut.
We've known each other for about 15 ~ 16 years. So I'll do my best.
You're know her not too long ago right?
Right, CocoYuno are the type to be aggressive.
I've been trying to find the right time to talk to her.
But at that time i've been watching you a lot. I'll do my best.
Well, Kobayashi...
That's right
"Friend" term is kind of...
A friend is also...
She's also my teacher.
That's right.
You're becoming a master and disciple.
My disciples  should understand me,
I will do my best in full of Yasumotoism.
This time, the one who gets the most correct answers,
I would like to award the title of Yasumoto King.
I'm a little nervous, too,
Let's get started right away!
I'm going to ask Yasumoto some questions now.
First, what is your favorite season?
We talk about this kind of thing quite a bit on the radio.
It's like we were talking about clothes in the lesson the other day.
It's an easy question.
Everyone should get 1 point, right?
Let's go
Let's look at them one by one.
Let's start with Mayama.
Autumn.
Autumn, right? That's when we talked about it.
Wasn't it?
I have the impression that it was a time of year when there were a lot of cloths.
Then, Nonoka.
Winter.
I remember hearing that it is good to have a lot of wet weather,
When  I said "I like winter, too", she said "That's righ" I remember the day when we talked about it.
Yes,  Kobayashi.
Summer.
Oh, now, the wind.
I don't know, the other day, when we were talking about clothes.
I don't know, Cocona likes summer.
And you're the one who was excited about it.
You said something about liking summer, too.
Maybe it's summer.
I think she said something like that.
Okay, okay.
Does it all fit with what you heard?
I don't know.
Well, you're all pretty much in the same boat.
Okay, let's look at the answer to the first question.
Okay.
What is your favorite season?
Autumn.
That's totally different.
Winter is also my favorite season.
Yes, it is.
Very much so.
But I'm not very good at it.
So, Autumn.
It's autumn. Mayama is right.
Thank you very much.
Don't you have a lot of pollen in autumn too?
But I'm sensitive to spring pollen.
I'm sensitive to it.
That's true.
But it's true i tell Nonoka that winter is good too.
and as Kaho said, summer is nice too. I think I said that,
but really it was autumn.
Thank you very much.
To make it easier to count the point, please write it down if you had correct answer.
Okay, I'll write it here.
So I would like to go to the next question.
It's fun.
Then, what is your favorite color?
I thought this question would come
I was expecting this one, cause i watched Yuna's  Yuna King
Favorite color?
What?
They're licking all over me.
Your favorite color? what is it?
You still confused of what my favorite color is?
Did You ever tell us about your favorite color?
Oh, but it's probably not something that comes up in conversation.
It's your favorite color.
But to be honest, I do have a favorite color.
I'm a little lost.
No, no, no, please decide.
I don't know how to say it.
Decide. But of course you've already decided.
It depends on your mood, doesn't it?
Yasumoto's...
I'm sure it's a number one.
Sometimes I say number two.
Why?
You only hear it once in three classes.
Surprising.
Okay, then.
Let's start with you, Mayama.
Here we go. This is it. Pink!
Oh!
Well, she was doing the "Kutstsuki bunbun" unit thing in Ebichu.
Her image color at the time was pink.
She didn't like it at the time.
It doesn't seem that she disliked it...
It's always been there.
I thought she might actually like pink.
So I also think that maybe Aya's girly inside is liking pink.
Oh, wow.
A secret pink lover.
I see.
Doesn't have to be secretly.
That's true.
Okay, then. Nonoka.
Green.
It's a member's color.
I've seen a lot of things with green tips and greenish hair, so I thought it was green.
And I chose red.
Oh, wow!
I know you like vivid colors.
I know what you mean.
Flashy.
But there are so many different flashy colors,
I thought I'd go with the standard red.
Let's look at the answers for a moment.
What is your favorite color?
Green.
Wow!
Really?
You looked kind of strange.
You looks like telling lies, just now.
Nonoka is right!!
If i were to asked (my favorite color) right away, I would definitely say green
The color you are given is like a mission, and since you are carrying that color, you can't help but choose it.
It has certainly increased over the years
I'm sure as Maya-san said i had a secret love of pink.
Oh, I see.
I didn't like pink when I was doing the Kutstsuki bunbun unit.
But after seeing that, I realized that pink is cute.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, right, so your second favorite color is...
Black.
No, it's not.
There's no pink in it.
Where is it?
It's hidden.
Kobayashi-san, please hang in there.
That's not good.
It's bad...
Three against three.
I'll do my best.
Let's continue.
What's your favorite hairstyle?
Oh!
What? - Uh... Uh, hair style? Oh?
Oh.
You mean hair arranging?
Not the length or anything.
Oh, including that.
Oh?
You like this hairstyle.
Yes, including that.
You've done a lot of things with it, haven't you, Aya?
Yes, indeed.
You certainly do a lot of things.
Okay, let's start with Mayama.
Yes, this way.
Illustration?
You know, like a foreign child.
It's a fluffy arrangement.
I think she likes to make her hair a little freckled
I think she likes it.
I see. I've been watching you for years.
I've seen it for years.
You're so excited when you do that.
The curly ones.
Then, I'm close with that too, the fluffy one.
I'm not so much like the fluffy ones, but I'm not so much like the gummy ones.
But I don't think it's too gwee, I think it's more relaxed.
A little bit mature. I see.
My answer also foreign children.
I think it's the most interesting aspect.
The sense of movement,
Yes, that's right.
The strong one.
By the way, only Nonoka is weak one.
I see.
Let's take a look at the answers.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
Short cut. I feel like changing my hair engine.
Why?
What?
It was a short cut in the big scheme of things.
So you arranged it first? You said you were going to include that.
You said something about including that, so I changed the arrangement, but it's not the same.
No, no, no.
It's totally different.
If you all had to name this haircut...
It's a short cut, right?
And you, Kobayashi?
Foreign child... A short cut
Then I'll give you points.
Thank you very much.
Did you answer "short cut" or "short cut"?
Or did you answer "mushroom head"?
Mushrooms seem to be difficult.
Mushrooms are kind of a big deal these days.
Mushrooms were booming too.
I'm just saying the answer is the same.
It's about me.
You've only had one stretch in the past.
It's only happened once.
I thought it was twice.
Finally, Kobayashi-san's point.
I got just a bonus points.
Thank you very much.
Is this your third or fourth?
That's all right.
Let's move on.
What?
Speaking of kings. What?
Speaking of kings.
Speaking of the king.
The king who is also in this project. The king of kings.
I think this is pretty easy.
Because I'm this no-nonsense person,
Oh, I got the clues together.
Please shut your mouth.
Did you get the answer? Yes, I did.
Here is my answer.
Ohsho
Ohsho Gyoza
And so on.
Aya's thoughts are often about food, so...
Osho?
something like that.
Yes, Crown.
I think it's pretty simple, just something that comes to mind.
I'm the Pirate King.
Oh!
I'm sure you're watching it, aren't you?
You like One Piece, right?
So I'm going to be the pirate king.
Oh, sure.
That's the image.
Well, let's see your answer.
What do you think of the king?
Me.
You're noisy.
What the hell.
What the hell?
This is the only thing I remember clearly: I said something that got me excited.
I feel like I'm a bit of an idiot for thinking about it so seriously...
I said it at the beginning, the atmosphere..
It's simple, something about yourself
So, there's no one got point this time.
How frustrating!
I'll be right in the middle of it.
Let's see the tally now.
The tally... I'm 2.
I'm 2.
I'm a one.
Oh.
I'm sorry about this.
You can make up for it.
I can make it up.
Yes, indeed, you can recover since you only changed by 1
I will do my best.
I'll do my best,
Yes, sir.
Please do your best, and let's see the results.
Yes.
Okay, let's continue.
What do you want to eat now?
Uh...
This is difficult.
This is difficult, isn't it?
I don't know when I got this.
I'm sure of its appearance,
June?
June? June.
June.
I'm speaking from my feelings at the time.
I don't remember.
I guess something i want to eat around June.
Hmmm...
Is there something i were into?
Ah! Oh! Wait!
I might have some confidence.
Oh! Oh, my gosh!
Something's coming.
I'm kind of looking for something in the conversation.
That's great! You're a great detective!
You're a great detective, Nonoka-chan!
Let's have her answer the question.
Maya-san!
Oyster!
I feel like it was rock oysters at this time.
I remember you're going there to eat.
You ate it so much... You've been addicted to it since the spring time.
I think it's rock oysters or sumi oysters.
Korean chicken... I have something to say... it's the end of June, right?
July 1st was Ibaraki Park for the Ibaraki Tour, wasn't it?
She was talking about how we were going to eat Korean chicken today after the Ibaraki Park tour.
You quite remember, right?
That's great!
That's why I thought so.
I see.
Great detective!
Great detective, Nonoka-chan.
It's just like that, isn't it?
Oh!
Korean Chicken
I remember you talking about wanting to have a Korean chicken party.
Sure, sure, sure.
It was about that time.
Wow, I don't know...
I don't know...
I don't know, right?
Let's check.
What do you want to eat now?
Ice cream.
Why... why ice cream?
Ice cream?
That's a very unexpected answer.
I was so surprised.
It's really about that moment
It's about this moment.
Why don't you just tell me what you think?
I don't understand this.
This is too difficult. I'm embarrassed.
It's difficult.
Then I'd like to go to the next question.
Yes.
What's the saddest thing you've done recently?
Saddest thing?
I don't know.
I think I answered this one pretty well.
Aya is a happy person, you know.
I didn't have a bad day,
It was really difficult.
That's right.
Please think about it while thinking about Yasumoto feeling.
I wonder what it is...
Start with Mayama.
When you try to open a bag of gummy bears, it goes "beep" and you can't open it after all.
It was rough, wasn't it?
Oh, it just beeped.
That's a little sad.
It's a little sad.
I wonder...
Nonoka, next.
Doraemon's pouch got dirty...
She brought it.
You know what you're talking about.
I remember you liking Doraemon.
I wonder what happened to it.
I carry around this kind of Doraemon drawstring pouch.
How did you know that?
It's embarrassing.
You've been observing me a lot.
She's looking...
Then, Mr. Kobayashi...
It was at a sudden cancellation
You were looking forward to it, but You were told "Sorry, it's so sudden, I can't do it!"
That's right, I've talked to Kaho several times about how angry I was after being canceled at the last minute.
You've been told that a lot.
I've been told quite a few times.
Because I said several times.
Yes, I have.
That's sad.
Yes, there are.
There are stories like that.
Well, I don't know if I can look back at this one either,
Let's both take a look.
Something that make you sad lately?
I just had lunch Korean dishes.
My hair smells really bad.
I don't know.
I don't care.
It's so stupid.
It's doesn't matter.
Maybe it was just a gal mind.
I thought I was gonna have a real problem with the smell.
I know, it's disgusting, but you can't win anymore, can you?
Then let's continue.
Where would you go on vacation?
What? But I think it's easy.
Easy?
I think so.
I'd be more nervous if you hadn't said something so twisted.
That's what I'm talking about.
What do you think?
I don't know.
If it's Yasumoto's charcoal cell, I'm sure...
I'm sure this is Yasumoto, too.
That's who this should be.
Then please, this is Korea.
If we talked about Korean food, I'd say "Korea.
There's too much single talent.
Nonoka.
Overseas.
Bigger.
I see.
Korea for me, too.
When She talk about Korea, she would said Korea next
She talked about Korea in the last question right?
Let's take a look.
Where would you go?
Korea!
I want to come to Korea when I come to Korea.
I want to buy a lot of cosmetics and do a lot of shopping.
It was a single cell
What about this one?
I'm a little bit worried about this one.
I was thinking Korea, by the way.
Oh...
I'm a little worried.
It's a little enlarged.
This one looks suspicious.
Leave it out.
Uh...
I'm going to be strict here.
Okay.
I want Nonokamaru to become strong too and become Yasumoto king.
How about it, Kobayashi?
Yes, I'm catching up!
Yes, I'm catching up with Nonokamaru.
Yes, so...
And that brings us to my last question.
Last question.
Oh, is that a score?
It's a routine.
Oh, that?
Uh, well, about this one.
It's a routine.
1,000 points!
Wow!
Let's go for it!
So, it was nothing until right now
But this, Mayama too...
Well, If i answer correctly, right? I see!
Right, you'll gonna have 1003 points.
Yes, I'm sure.
Totally.
Okay, let's finish up!
So, what are you into these days?
What I'm into these days.
What are you into these days?
Well, I'm a little... I'm a little...
Which one? Which one did I say?
What I'm into these days is the most difficult one.
Aya, you have many hobbies.
You like sauna,
You also like beauty care,
You also have DTM.
Oh, I don't know...
You mean the truce in June, right?
Yes, that's right.
Then, please make an announcement.
First of all, here it is.
It's a girlfriend-like insta-post.
I don't know when it started but Aya started posting pictures of herself 10 steps in front, and it kind of gives me the impression that she's a girlfriend.
I see. So I remember that you took pictures quite often during the tour.
I remember that i was posting pictures quite often during the tour and birthday.
I was posting videos of girlfriend-like with my original songs.
Then, cooking...
She's been posting Instagram stories.
What she cook? with Aya-chan's plate hashtag?
Yes, I've seen it a few times, so I don't know if that's when she got into it.
I don't know if that's what got me hooked on cooking, because sometimes i would suddenly start doing that to stay healthy while i was on tour.
Beauty skincare
She's a skin care expert. What are you into these days?
Let's see the answer.
What are you into these days?
What am I into these days?
Lookism.
Student anime set in Korea
Don't give me that un-un
I know what you mean.
This is a anime I used to watch and not tell anybody.
There is no chance we can get it.
It's not often I get into anime or manga.
It's not often.
This is hard.
I just remembered that I was into it too.
This was so much fun.
I kind of watched it in like three days, like a gulp. It was a lot of fun.
You were watching it in real time.
That's right.
you're into it
I don't know.
So, you all have zero points,
Zero points.
You had your chance. I want you to be safe.
I don't know.
You didn't tell me. You know what I mean.
So, who won the title of Yasumoto king this time?
Rika Mayama.
Thank you very much.
Mayama-san, 3 points.
Nonoka-san, 2 points.
Kobayashi-san 3 points.
So, that's it,
Mayama been here for me for16 years,
I'm spending the most time in a long time,
I'm very happy to receive the title of Yasumoto king.
But Yasumoto-san, don't answer the question yourself.
You don't remember at all
I'm often surprised by the things I do
As a Yasumoto king, You can use this title anywhere.
that's nice
In your resume? Resume?
You can have it in your resume.
That's nice.
2023 Yasumoto.
You can had it written in materials for auditions etc.
Who's going through it?
what's this?
By the way...
What's the one question you don't want them to miss?
"Speaking of King"
Why???
I want them to say me
I want everyone to support me.
Don't give me that "Heh heh heh"
I think everyone loves Yasumoto so much.
I'm sure you'll be able to answer in plenty of time.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
So...
I'm getting a little carried away that day.
It's a little bit awkward face after you done saying it.
like stop it.
If you're on a roll, stay on a roll until the end!
I was a little embarrassed because I had one-on-one time with the staff.
How many years have you been doing it?
I'm sure you can answer that in plenty of time, can't you?
So, you see, everyone, today you thought once of the Yasumoto thing,
I'm  glad.
I'm glad.
I want to update it again.
I would like to do Yasumoto king again someday,
Mayama-san, please don't lose Yasumoto king title,
Yes, that's right.
Please keep observing.
Okay, I understand.
Nonaka-san, you seem to have a pretty good sense.
I hope you will keep up your good work.
I think you can be the king.
I think so.
Kobayashi-san, from now on too please keep up the good work.
Please keep up the good work.
I will do my best for the last one.
That's all for Yasumoto King. Good button, please subscribe to our channel!
I'm also waiting for your comments.
Bye bye!
Bye bye.
Good.
Make it Good.
Make it Good. Bye!